# Júlia Rouxinol

# **Product Designer**

I'm focused on designing creative and meaningful digital experiences through user-centered methodologies. My workflow focuses on co-working on an end-to-end project process using an open mindset, a critical sense, and a heavily research-based and creative approach.

jurouxinol@gmail.com +351 936648376 jurouxinol.com/ /in/jurouxinol/

# Experience

#### Kito Health - UX/UI Designer

March 2022 - Present | Lisbon, PT

- Supported the UX Lead auxiliating in operational tasks
- Collaborated with developers and product manager to assess project outcomes and prioritize future app features;

#### Vodafone - UX/UI Designer Intern

September 2021 - March 2022 | Lisbon, PT

Consumer Business Unit - Tribe Digital Channels.

- Supported the UX team in different products that included the My Vodafone App and Desktop, Vodafone's website and E-shop
- Conducted 20+ user-testing and interviews related to 3 different products
- Worked on the Design System helping the migration of components to Figma and in the creation of new ones
- Created user interface designs, prototypes and proposed user journeys
- Collaborated with PM's, designers, and stakeholders using a human-centric design approach

### Education & Courses

## Digital Experience Design - Post Graduation

September 2021 - Present, Lisbon, PT Faculdade de Belas Artes da ULisboa

The course spans two semesters and is composed of a set of mandatory and optional units, with a total of 60 ECTS. It's focused on learning to design, build and launch cutting-edge digital products and services.

#### **UX/UI Intensive Course**

January 2021 - September 2021, Remote Awari

Online Bootcamp that spans 8 month. The course has 410 hours of classes.

#### Global Design - Bachelor's Degree

September 2018 - July 2021, Lisbon, PT IADE - Creative University

The course spans six semesters and is composed of a set of mandatory units with a total of 180 ECTS. The course focuses on several areas of design — Product Design, UX Design, UI Design, among others.

#### Skills

#### Knowledge

User Experience Design . Visual Design . User Research . Usability Testing . Design Thinking . Sketching/Wireframing . Prototyping . I Conception/Development

#### **Tools**

Figma . Sketch . Zeplin . Invision . Miro . Adobe Suite . HTML, CSS and JavaScript (beginner)

#### Languages

Portuguese (native). English (fluent). French (beginner)